If we're stardust.
If we're just a grain of sand.
In the vastness of the universe.
Hold your breath
inside the earnestness of time.
If we're just a fleeting sponge.
The stars above.
God, what a lucky man I am to inform you.
Lovely grain.
Sand.
In the vastness of the universe.
If only your breath
inside the endless center.
If it's just a fleeting star.
Come on. The stars above.
Out of millions of stars.
Somehow I was lucky enough to find you.
God, what a lucky man I am to strike.
Just a minute.
On the back of the sands of time.
Every skin falls
and we can't ever make it stop.
We can't stop time.
But we can choose
to spend this life together.
I want to dance with you tonight.
With the light star to shine inside.
With each other.
Plus the music of the company. Me.
We didn't choose.
When we go out on this dance for laughs.
But if we ever get out there
tonight.
Let's dance.
I pray it's living.
And life is just a minute.
I want every sacrifice, you know.
And when you do,
you wanna know what the universe is.
Writing out a story.
I don't know what it has in store for us.
I don't know if it was decent.
You. Just a beautiful coincidence.
The bodies face to face.
All I know is we're building
something together.
Let us beat you with a choice
we make together.
Walking side by side
through the past two days
I want to discover every corner
of your universe.
Made of stardust.
Let me discover in you
how long it's gonna take you.
Let shows the price.
The music of the company we didn't choose
I wish I know
how long this dance will last.
But it's way together.
Tonight.
Let's dance up
here.
Let's look at this.
Living up.
I don't like this. Just a minute.
I want every sacrifice.
I can do it with you.
Oh, I want you for this
lifetime and for eternity.
I want to stay inside your heart
every single day.
I want to write a story in the stars.
Look up at the sky and see it
shining there.
Maybe turning it on forever.
But one moment
when you can make forever feel.
Even in the middle of all this chaos.
I want to hold your hand.
Even if the whole world changes.
Even if I can't find the love later.
That's I want to be this better.
When I say spend our universe
I've got so many dimensions
I want to show you.
And so many emotions
that you awakened in me.
Let's go to the moon and sit here
together.
Let's invent something
no one's ever known.
The universe seems so vast.
But tonight, if it's entirely true,
you guys, I want to kiss.
As I start, I feel your skin travel
through your car place.
Just love me.
Make you feel like you belong among them.
Let me build for you a corridor of stars.
And I feel you to admire
that I build you a brand new.
Oh, I just want to gather your planets
and comets.
If you show me your darkness. I like to.
Why can't I just stars?
I want to know your love, your shadows,
your stars and your galaxies.
I want to discover
every corner of your universe.
I don't want others to start us.
Even in your darkest night.
I'll learn how to find you.
I want to close my eyes
and feel your lips against mine.
Give me the eternity of your kisses.
Every human could
I want to discover them. Oh,
without thinking about time.
Without thinking about tomorrow.
Oh, just you and me
now I'll make it tonight.
It doesn't mean forever.
I want all the ways
you can never ever feel you
I love star, love me.
Discover in you how long.
It's kind of love.
Oh, I want to know what it feels like.
When the universe falls in love.
And then some time
we reach the edge of the universe.
I want to know the end of it.
With you by my side.
Because I don't want to stop.
So I'm.
I don't want to ask you to stand still.
My mom.
I want to live.
And I want to live with you.
Just the price that you say
nothing compares with you to.
Just like me. I wonder how on this night.
So much fun for you to trouble the moon.
Oh, let's dance
its way here.
Let's live it. Set it.
To life.
It's just a
clock of a sense of time.
I want every second of it with you.
And if it's just a fleeting spark
among the stars.
But I know your stars.